allquestions=[
  {
    question:"what is the color of water??",
    options:["green","blue","red","orange"],
    correct:1
  },
  {
    question:"what is the color of blood??",
    options:["black","white","grey","red"],
    correct:3
  },
  {
    question:"what is the color of milk??",
    options:["black","white","grey","red"],
    correct:1
  },
  {
    question:"what is the color of rose??",
    options:["black","white","grey","red"],
    correct:3
  },
  {
    question:"what is the color of hair??",
    options:["black","white","grey","red"],
    correct:0
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented JavaScript?",
    options: ["Douglas Crockford","Sheryl Sandberg","Brendan Eich","none of above" ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of these is a JavaScript package manager?",
    options: ["Node.js","TypeScript","npm", "none of above"
    ],
    correct:2
  },
  {
    question: "Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
    options: ["Angular","jQuery","RequireJS","ESLint"],
    correct:3
  },
  {
   question: "Who is Peter Parker’s nemesis in the first Spider-Man film?",
   options:["The Joker", "Magneto", "The Green Goblin","None"],
   correct:3
  },
  {
   question: "What is Cyclops’ power in X-Men?",
   options:["Telekinesis", "Optic blast", " Diamond skin", "all"],
   correct:2
  },
  {
   question: "What is the name of the cosmic cube that Loki takes control of in The Avengers?",
   options:["the Tesseract", "the Magic Cube", "the Mjolnir", "all"],
   correct:1
  },
  {
   question: "How many Avengers are there in the Avengers movie?",
   options:[" 4", " 10", "6", "100"],
   correct:3
  },
  {
   question: "How do the Fantastic Four get their powers?",
   options:["  they were bitten by a radioactive spider", " they were exposed to cosmic radiation in space", " they were experimented on", "Dont know"],
   correct:2
  },
  {
   question: " What’s the name of Tony Stark’s company in the Iron Man trilogy?",
   options:["  Stark and Sons", "  Stark and Co", " Stark Industries", "Avg co"],
   correct:3
  },
  {
   question:"Who does Dare Devil team up with in his film?",
   options:[" Elektra", "  Storm", "The Invisible Woman", "Wonder Women"],
   correct:1
  },
  {
   question:"How many years was Captain America frozen for in Captain America: The First Avenger?",
   options:[" Nearly 100 years", " Nearly 70 years", "Nearly 20 years", "Nearly 10 years"],
   correct:2
  },
  {
   question:"Who is Thor’s main romantic interest in Thor?",
   options:["Jane Foster", "Jean Grey", "Mary Jane", "peta Jenson"],
   correct:1
  },
  {
   question:" In X2, who do the X-Men find hidden in a church?",
   options:["The Nightcrawler", "The Silver Surfer", "The beast", "Monkey Man"],
   correct:3
  },
  {
   question:" What’s the name of Jean Grey’s alter-ego in X-Men?",
   options:[" The Black Widow", "The Invisible Woman", "The Phoenix", "The Hulk"],
   correct:2
  },
  {
   question:"What is the name of Rhodey’s iron suit in Iron Man 3",
   options:["Death Proof", "  War Machine", " Killing Machine", "Jump Suit"],
   correct:1
  }
  ];